Guide to the Winterhouse Art and Design Collection of Volume 1 Number 1
Yale University Arts Library
- Examples, 1919-2011; Series II
  - The Journal of Typographic Research. Volume One: Number One. Cleveland: Western Reserve University, January 1967. pp. 112. (Box 3, Folder 126)
    Article of note: "Effects of Three Variables on Speed of Reading."
    Design by Jack Stauffacher.
  - KOS. Anno I, Numero 1. Milan: Franco Maria Ricci, February 1984. pp. 128. (Box 3, Folder 127)
    Contributions by Ferdinando Abbri, W.R. Albury, Nigel Allan and Ned Bloch.
    Article of note: "Il Mal Francese."
  - Language Learning: A Quarterly Journal of Applied Linguistics. Volume I: Number I. Ann Arbor, Michigan: University of Michigan Press, January 1948. pp. 32. (Box 3, Folder 128)
    Edited by David W. Reed.
    Contributions by Charles C. Fries, Robert Lado and Yao Shen.
    Article of note: "Motives for the Study of Modern Languages."
    Cover design by Graciela Galup.
  - The Larcom Review: A Journal of the Arts and Literature. Volume One: Issue One. Prides Crossing, Massachusetts: Larcom Press, Spring–Summer 1999. pp. 272. (Box 4, Folder 129)
    Edited by Susan Oleksiw.
    Contributions by Deborah Barbour, Kat Meads and Karen Skolfield.
    Article of note: "Andre Dubus Remembered."
  - Leftside. Issue One. Stratford, England: Leftside, 2000. pp. 30. (Box 4, Folder 130)
    Edited by Kyn and Cai Taylor.
    Contributions by Phil Baines, Melody Wong and Julia Woollams.
    Article of note: "Interview." Design by Kyn and Cai Taylor.
  - Legal Affairs: A Magazine of Yale Law School. Volume 1: Number 1. New Haven: Legal Affairs, June 2002. pp. 72. (Box 4, Folder 131)
    Edited by Lincoln Caplan.
    Contributions by Dashka Slater, Asha Rangappa and Bill Rankin.
    Articles of note: "Let There Be Law," and "From Russia With Løpht."
    Design by William Drenttel and Jessica Helfand, Winterhouse.
  - Life. Volume 1: Number 1. Chicago: Time Inc., November 23, 1936. pp. 96. (Box 7, Folder 254)
    Edited by Henry R. Luce, John Shaw Billings and Daniel Longwell.
    Contribution by Robert E. Fulton, Jr.
    Article of note: "Franklin Roosevelt's Wild West."
  - Litchfield Magazine. Premiere Issue. Litchfield, Connecticut: Morris Media Group, Spring 2008. pp. 80. (Box 4, Folder 132)
    Edited by Geoffrey James Morris.
    Contributions by Amanda Bergen, Andrea DiNoto and Nick Wedge.
    Article of note: "Real Deal."
    Design by Deborah Hayn.
  - The Litchfield Review. Volume 1: Number 1. Beacon Falls, Connecticut: The Litchfield Review, Winter 2004. pp. 66. (Box 4, Folder 133)
    Edited by Mary Donnarumma Sharnick and Theresa C. Vara.
    Contributions by Patricia Klindienst, Ed Frankel and Douglas W. Lawder.
    Article of note: "The Doe."
    Cover photograph by Christopher M. Dannen.
  - Literary Imagination: The Review of the Association of Literary Scholars and Critics. Volume One: Number One. Athens, Georgia: University of Georgia, Spring 1999. pp. 169. (Box 4, Folder 134)
    Edited by Sarah Spence.
    Contributions by Mark Strand W. S. Merwin and Robert Alter.
    Article of note: "Arguments with God."
    Design by Hecht Design.
  - Locus Solus. Number One. Lans-en-Vercors, France: Locus Solus Press, 1960. pp. 168. (Box 4, Folder 135)
    Edited by John Ashbery, Kenneth Koch, Harry Mathews and James Schuyler.
    Contributions by Edwin Denby, Barbara Guest and Frank O'Hara.
    Article of note: "Current Events."
  - Log: Observations on Architecture and the Contemporary City. Number One. New York: Anyone Corporation, Fall 2003. pp. 152. (Box 4, Folder 136)
    Edited by Cynthia Davidson.
    Contributions by Julie Rose, Mark Taylor, Bernard Tschumi and Paul Virilio.
    Article of note: "How the World Became a Real Fake."
    Design consultation by Michael Bierut.
  - MHQ: Quarterly Journal of Military History. Volume One: Number One. New York: MHQ, Autumn 1988. pp. 128. (Box 4, Folder 137)
    Edited by Robert Cowley.
    Contributions by John Keegan, Geoffrey Parker and Stephen Sears.
    Article of note: "A Short History of the Management of Violence."
    Design by Marleen Adlerblum.
  - Main Group Chemistry. Volume One: Number One. Amsterdam: Overseas Publishers Association, 1995. pp. 172. (Box 4, Folder 138)
    Edited by David Atwood.
    Contributions by George Koutsantonis, Fu Chin Lee and Colin Raston.
    Article of note: "Structural Diversity in Organoindium Iodides."
  - Mainstream: A Literary Quarterly. Volume One: Number One. New York: Mainstream, Winter 1947. pp. 128. (Box 4, Folder 139)
    Edited by Samuel Sillen.
    Contributions by Frederick Engels, Langston Hughes and Dalton Trumbo.
    Article of note: "Partisan Review: Esthetics of the Cage."
  - Map Forum. Issue One. London: Countrywide Editions, Spring 2004. pp. 74. (Box 4, Folder 140)
    Edited by Ashley Baynton-Williams.
    Contributions by Debbie Hall, Jonathan Potter and Rodney Shirley.
    Article of note: "A Checklist of Printed Plans of Washington D.C. 1792–1801."
    Design by Countrywide Editions.
  - Timothy McSweeney's Quarterly Concern. Issue One. New York: McSweeney's Publishing Concern, Autumn 1998. pp. 144. (Box 4, Folder 141)
    Edited by David Eggers.
    Contributions by Komar & Melamid, Mia Fineman, Rick Moody, Todd Pruzan and David Foster Wallace.
    Article of note: "Old Dogs, New Tricks. The Twilight of Modernism, and the Dawn of the Neo-Senilists."
    Design by David Eggers.
  - Medical Details. Volume One: Number One. Rahway, New Jersey: Merck, June 1952. pp. 26. (Box 4, Folder 142)
    Article of note: "Hydrocortone in Osteoarthritis."
  - Medical Heritage. Volume One: Number One. Philadelphia: W.B. Saunders, January/February 1985. pp. 80. (Box 4, Folder 143)
    Edited by Sharon Romm.
    Contributions by Richard Selzer, Donald W. Faulkner and Ron Kleemann.
    Article of note: "Immortal Quackery."
    Cover art by Jim Dine.
  - Men's Journal. Issue One. New York: Straight Arrow, May–June 1992. pp. 176. (Box 7, Folder 255)
    Edited by John Rasmus and Jann S. Wenner.
    Contributions by Roy Blount Jr., Chip Brown and Donald Katz.
    Article of note: "Greatness on Ice."
    Design by Matthew Drace.
  - Mined Magazine. Issue One. London: Tank Publications, May 2001. pp. 480. (Box 4, Folder 144)
    Edited by Masoud Golsorkhi, Andreas Laeufer and Ekow Eshun.
    Contributions by Claire Channing, Tom Dixon, Julian Schnabel and Alison Whelan.
    Article of note: "On Transcendence with Ang Lee."
    Design by Andreas Laeufer.
  - The Minetta Review. Number One. New York: New York University, Fall 2001. pp. 64. (Box 4, Folder 145)
    Edited by Eric Sillman.
    Contributions by Katy Ball and Lindsay Reckson.
    Article of note: "Party Poem."
    Design by Eric Skillman.
  - Minimal Politics: Performativity and Minimalism in Recent American Art. Number One. Baltimore: University of Maryland, September 1997. pp. 162. (Box 4, Folder 146)
    Edited by Maurice Berger.
    Contributions by Hans Haacke, Robert Morris, Adrian Piper and Yvonne Rainer.
    Article of note: "Minimal Politics 1965–1995: A Timeline of American Politics, Race, Gender and Sexuality."
    Design by Franc Nunoo-Quarcoo.
  - Mirabella. Issue One. New York: Murdoch, June 1989. pp. 268. (Box 4, Folder 147)
    Edited by Grace Mirabella and Amy Gross.
    Contributions by Michael O'Neill, Phyllis Rose and Frank Rich.
    Article of note: "Start-ups."
    Design by Jade Hobson Charnin.
  - Modern Graphic Design. Number One. Cincinnati: J. W. Ford Company, Fall 1955. pp. 24. (Box 7, Folder 256)
    Edited by Edward H. Dwight.
    Article of note: "Graphic Design in Switzerland."
    Design by Noel Martin.
  - Monocle. Issue 01. Volume 01. London: Winkontent Limited, March 2007. pp. 242. (Box 4, Folder 148)
    Edited by Tyler Brûlé.
    Contributions by Steve Bloomfield, Akio Hasegawa and Joachim Bessing.
    Article of note: "Light Fantastic."
    Design by Richard Spencer Powell.
  - n+1. Number One. New York: n+1 Research, Fall 2004. pp. 182. (Box 4, Folder 149)
    Edited by Keith Gessen, Mark Greif, Benjamin Kunkel and Marco Roth.
    Contributions by Masha Gessen, Patrick Giles and Joshua Glenn.
    Article of note: "McSweeney's: A Regressive Avant-Garde."
    Design by Ryan Haley.
  - The National Grid. Number One. Auchland, NZ: National Grid, March 2006. pp. 96. (Box 4, Folder 150)
    Edited by Jonty Valentine and Luke Wood.
    Contributions by Aaron Beehre, Harold Grieves and James Maxwell.
    Article of note: "Putting NZ Communication Design on the Map."
    Design by Jonty Valentine and Luke Wood.
  - Nebo: A Literary Journal. Number One. Russellville, Arkansas: Arkansas Tech University, 1980. pp. 60. (Box 4, Folder 151)
    Edited by Judith Clark and Anne Marie Hamby.
    Contributions by Dana Gioia, Glenda Schrock and Harold Witt.
    Article of note: "Rate of Exchange."
  - The New Criterion. Volume One: Number One. New York: Foundation for Cultural Review, September 1982. pp. 96. (Box 4, Folder 152)
    Edited by Hilton Kramer.
    Contributions by Elias Canetti, Joseph Epstein and Norman Podhoretz.
    Article of note: "Postmodern: The 1980s."
    Design by Alvin and James Eisenman.
  - New Times: A Journal of World Affairs. Number One. Moscow: Trud, January 1966. pp. 32. (Box 4, Folder 153)
    Edited by Natalia Sergeyeva.
    Contributions by Rockwell Kent, A. Leonidov and R. Selucky.
    Article of note: "American Intellectuals and the Problems of War and Peace."
  - New Work. Volume One: Number One. New York: Studio NewWork, Autumn/Winter 2007. 7 sections. (Box 7, Folder 257)
    Edited by Ryotatsu Tanaka, Ryyo Kumazaki and Hitomi Ishigaki.
    Contributions by Tiziano Magni, Yuji Takenaka and Naoki Asai.
    Article of note: "Man Who Wants to Fly."
    Design by Studio NewW0000000ork.
  - The New York Journal of American History. Volume One: Number One. New York: New York Historical Society, Spring 2003. pp. 128. (Box 4, Folder 154)
    Edited by Valerie Paley.
    Contributions by Kenneth T. Jackson, Sandra Markham and Steven Mintz.
    Article of note: "The Great Fire of 1835."
    Design by K. T. Meaney.
    Formerly The New York Historical Society Quarterly. Volume Sixty-Five: Number One.
  - New York Magazine. Volume One: Number One. New York: New York Magazine, April 1968. pp. 132. (Box 4, Folder 155)
    Edited by Clay S. Felker.
    Contributions by Milton Glaser, Jerome Snyder and Gloria Steinem.
    Article of note: "Ho Chi Minh in New York."
    Design by Milton Glaser.
  - The Next American City: The Future of Smart Growth. Premiere Issue. New York: The Next American City, Spring 2003. pp. 48. (Box 4, Folder 156)
    Edited by Adam Gordon.
    Contributions by Kent Bloomer, Jason Moses and Shayna Strom.
    Article of note: "The Growth Explosion."
    Design by Jayme Yen.
  - Nextbook Reader: Culture & Ideas. Number One. New York: Nextbook, Fall 2005. pp. 16. (Box 7, Folder 258)
    Edited by Blake Eskin and Sara Ivry.
    Contributions by Shalom Auslander, Sherwin Neland and Stephen Vider.
    Article of note: "Raising King David: Interview with Robert Pinsky."
  - Nine: A Journal of Baseball History and Social Perspectives. Volume 1: Number 1. Edmonton, Canada: University of Alberta Press, Fall 1992. pp. 120. (Box 4, Folder 157)
    Edited by Bill Kirwin.
    Contributions by Don Albrecht, Peter Carino and Mark Savoie.
    Article of note: "Baseball Performance and the Relative Age Effect: Does Little League Neutralize Birthdate Selection Process."
  - No 1: Interface Flor Folio. Number One. Cohoes, New York: Interface Flor, 2008. pp. 52. (Box 4, Folder 158)
    Contributions by Dianna Edwards, Starsky + Cox and Walter Thomas.
    Article of note: "Mission Possible."
    by Robert Valentine.
  - Normal: A Quarterly of Arts and Ideas. Number One. New York: Normal, Summer 1986. pp. 96. (Box 7, Folder 259)
    Edited by Gini Alhadeff.
    Contributions by Ivo Andric, Umberto Eco, Kenneth Frampton and Massimo Scolari.
    Article of note: "The Desert: The Diary of Beirut Under Seige."
    Design by Paul Davis.
  - The Nose: Graphic Commentary. Number One. New York: Pushpin Group, 1997. pp. 16. (Box 4, Folder 159)
    Edited by DK Holland.
    Contributions by Steven Brower, Seymour Chwast and James Victore.
    Article of note: "A Little Knowledge."
    Design by Seymour Chwast.
  - O: The Oprah Magazine. Volume One: Number One. New York: Hearst, May–June 2000. pp. 318. (Box 4, Folder 160)
    Edited by Oprah Winfrey and Ellen Kunes.
    Contributions by Veronica Chambers, Elizabeth Kim and Stephanie Saulmon.
    Article of note: "Oprah Talks to Camille Cosby."
    Design by Carla Frank.
  - Octavo: Journal of Typography. Number One. London: Eight Five Zero, December 1986. pp. 16. (Box 4, Folder 161)
    Edited and designed by Simon Johnston, Mark Holt, Michael Burke and Hamish Muir.
    Contributions by April Greiman, Robin Kinross and David Reason.
    Article of note: "Richard Long's Art of Words."
    Design by Optic.
  - October: Art, Theory, Criticism, Politics. Number One. New York: Institute for Architecture and Urban Studies, Spring 1976. pp. 112. (Box 4, Folder 162)
    Edited by Jeremy Gilbert-Rolfe, Rosalind Krauss and Annette Michaelson.
    Contributions by Noel Burch, Michel Foucault and Hollis Franpton.
    Article of note: "Gravity's Rainbow and the Spiral Jetty."
    Design by Charles Read.
  - Off Ramp. Volume One: Number One. Santa Monica: SCI-ARC, Spring 1988. pp. 42. (Box 4, Folder 163)
    Edited by SCI-ARC students.
    Contributions by Steve Barry, Tom Buresh and Mark Mack.
    Article of note: "Bodybuildings by Elizabeth Diller and Ricardo Scofidio."
  - Omnivore: A Journal of Writing & Visual Culture. Volume One: Number One. New York: New York Institute for the Humanities at NYU, Autumn 2003. pp. 176. (Box 4, Folder 164)
    Edited by Lawrence Weschler.
    Contributions by Rachel Cohen, David Hockney, Siri Hustvedt, Errol Morris, Oliver Sacks and Rebecca Solnit.
    Article of note: "Women's Bodies in the Landscape."
    Cover photograph by Victor Schrager.
  - Open Manifesto: Thoughts on Graphic Design. Number One. Sydney, Australia: Manifesto Group, 2004. pp. 104. (Box 5, Folder 165)
    Edited by Kevin Finn.
    Contributions by Craig Bremner, Émilie de Comarmond and Vince Frost.
    Article of note: "The Incredible Lightness of Being in Australia."
    Design by Kevin Finn.
  - Overflow: A Magazine of Poetry. Volume One: Number One. Ann Arbor: University of Michigan, August 1967. pp. 56. (Box 5, Folder 166)
    Edited by Richard Taylor.
    Contributions by Ronald Bodnar, John Kelly and Richard Taylor.
    Poem of note: "Autumn Day."
    Design by John Kelly and Ronald Bodnar.
  - Palimpsest, Yale Literary and Arts Magazine. Volume 1: Number 1. New Haven: Yale University, April, 2003. pp. 128. (Box 7, Folder 260)
    Edited by Won Jung Park.
    Contributions by Brian R. Moore, Aaron Sachs and Ravi Hampole.
    Article of note: "Burning Effigies of American Presidents."
    Design by Alexander S. Budnix.
  - Paper Monument: A Journal of Contemporary Art. Number One. Brooklyn: Paper Monument, Fall 2007. pp. 82. (Box 5, Folder 167)
    Edited by Dushko Petrovich and Roger White.
    Contributions by Katie Sonnenborn, Roger White and David Kearns.
    Article of note: "Peter Nagy from New Delhi."
    Design by Project Projects.
  - Parkett: Art Magazine. Number One. Zurich: Parkett Verlag, April 1984. pp. 116. (Box 5, Folder 168)
    Edited by Bice Curiger.
    Contributions by Jacqueline Burckhardt, Enzo Cucchi and Barbara Kruger.
    Article of note: "The History of Art—Dead or Alive?"
    Design by Trix Wetter.
  - Partisan Review: A Bi-Monthly of Revolutionary Literature. Volume One: Number One. New York: John Reed Club, February–March 1934. pp. 64. (Box 5, Folder 169)
    Edited by Nathan Adler, Edward Dahlberg and Joseph Freeman.
    Contributions by James T. Farrell, Philip Rahv and Edwin Rolfe.
    Article of note: "The Anatomy of Liberalism."
    Design by Elroy Webber.
  - Persimmon: Asian Literature, Arts and Culture. Volume One: Number One. New York: Contemporary Asian Culture, Spring 2000. pp. 112. (Box 5, Folder 170)
    Edited by Caroline Herrick.
    Contributions by Germeie Barmé, Pramoedya Toer and Tserendash Namkhainyambuu.
    Article of note: "Memoirs of A Mongolian Herder."
    Design by Emil Antonucci.
  - PIN-UP: Magazine for Architectural Entertainment. Issue 1. New York: Febu Publishing, Fall 2006. pp. 96. (Box 5, Folder 171)
    Edited by Felix Burrichter.
    Contributions by Anuschka Blommers, Nicholas Boston and Edward Buchanan.
    Article of note: "Zaha Hadid: PIN-UP gets up to speed with architecture's most beloved diva."
    Design by Dylan Fracareta and Geoffrey Han.
  - Pluck: The Journal of Affrilachian Arts and Culture. Issue One. Cincinnati: Duncan Hill Press, 2007. pp. 54. (Box 5, Folder 172)
    Edited by Frank X Walker.
    Contributions by C.M. Burroughs and Kelly Norman Ellis.
    Article of note: "Black Mountain: The Affrilachian Literary Tradition."
    Design by Amanda Brown.
  - DesignIndia POOL: India's First International Design Magazine. Number 01. Indian Edition. India: INDI Design Pvt, July 2010. pp. 28. (Box 5, Folder 173)
    Edited by Sudhir Sharma.
    Contributions by Lulu Raghaven, Tejas Modak and Tsutomu Sato.
    Article of note: "Fortune at the bottom of the pyramid."
    Design by Pradeep Arora.
  - Positions: Modern Architecture and Urbanism. Issue Zero. Amsterdam: NAi Publishers, 2008. pp. 96. (Box 5, Folder 174)
    Edited by Sarah Williams Goldhagen, Eric Mumford and Cor Wagenaar.
    Contributions by Tim Benton and Bohdan Tscherkes.
    Article of note: "X-ray Architecture: Illness as Metaphor."
    Design by Joseph Plateau.
  - Praxis: Journal of Writing + Building. Volume One: Issue Zero. New York: Praxis, Fall 1999. pp. 126. (Box 5, Folder 175)
    Edited by Amanda Reeser and Ashley Schafer.
    Contributions by Stan Allen, Vittorio Garatti and Bernard Tschumi.
    Article of note: "IIT Beyond Mies: A New Urban Focus."
    Design by Brad Bell and Ronald Rael.
  - Primal Community. Volume One: Number One. Durham, Connecticut: International Primal Association, Summer 1974. pp. 48. (Box 5, Folder 176)
    Edited by Richard Greeman.
    Contributions by Jean Getoff, David Konstan and Hy Weiner.
    Article of note: "Innovations in Primal-Oriented Therapy: The All-Sound Method."
    Design by Diane Dixon and Jim Dixon.
  - P.S.: The Quarterly Journal of the Poster Society. Volume One. Upper Montclair, New Jersey: The Poster Society, Winter 1985/86. pp. 32., 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 177)
    Edited by Robert K. Brown.
    Contributions by Ida Katherine Rigby, Ivan Chermayeff and George M. Dembo.
    Article of note: "The Statue of Liberty in Posters."
    Design by George Tscherny.
  - Psychological Issues. Volume One: Number One. New York: International Universities Press, 1959. pp. 184. (Box 5, Folder 178)
    Edited by George Klein.
    Contributions by Erik H. Erikson and David Rapaport.
    Article of note: "Growth and Crisis of the Healthy Personality."
  - Pub: The CalArts Graphic Design Student Publication. Volume One: Issue One. Valencia, California: California Institute of the Arts, Fall 2007. (Box 5, Folder 179)
    Edited by Gilbert Avila, Aaron Axelrod, Ashley Cunningham, MacGregor Harp, Victor Hu, Kurtis Kennington, Julie Mattei, Caroline Oh and Allbriton Robbins.
    Contributions by Victor Hu, Gilbert Avila and Julie Mattei.
    Article of note: "Fella Collections."
    Design by Julie Mattei.
  - A Public Space. Volume One: Issue One. New York: A Public Space Literary Projects, Spring 2006. pp. 224. (Box 5, Folder 180)
    Edited by Brigid Hughes.
    Contributions by Rick Moody, Haruki Murakami and Michael Palmer.
    Article of note: "Inspired by a True Story."
    Design by Roger Bova.
  - Pulse Berlin. Number One. Berlin: Pulse, 2005. pp. 130. (Box 5, Folder 181)
    Edited by Andrea K. Hiott.
    Contributions by Bradley Bassler, Michele Sala and Irwin M. Stelzer.
    Article of note: "Some Tentative Thoughts on Immigration."
    Design by Nicola Gerndt.
  - Q1: A Publication of the Yale School of Management. Q1. New Haven: Yale School of Management, Spring 2007. pp. 122. (Box 5, Folder 182)
    Edited by Jonathan T.F. Weisberg.
    Contributions by Jeffrey Pfeffer, Trish Karter and James N. Baron.
    Article of note: "How Do you Manage a Global Financial Crisis?."
    Design by 2X4.
  - R.24: The Magazine of Renaissance Hotels. Premier Issue. New York: American Express Publishing, 2010. pp. 58. (Box 7, Folder 261)
    Edited by Liz Buffa.
    Contribution by Bruce Schoenfeld, Barbara Rowley and Anya Von Bremzen.
    Article of note: "The New Wave in French Cooking."
    Design by Jenny Knight.
  - Rana. Number 1. Sunnyvale, California: Rana Publishing, 1994. pp. 80. (Box 5, Folder 183)
    Edited by Phil Patton.
    Contributions by Uta Brandes, Hartmut Esslinger and Stuart Green.
    Article of note: "Interdisciplinary = Interdependency."
    Design by Steven Skov Holt and Gregory Hom.
  - Rattapallax: A Journal of Contemporary Literature. Number One. New York: Repossessed Head Press, 1999. pp. 128. (Box 5, Folder 184)
    Edited by George Dickerson.
    Contributions by Michael Graves, Alexis Winter and Arnold Joseph Wohl.
    Article of note: "The Love Song of Chester Whitherspoon."
    Design by Robert Harding.
  - RayGun. Issue One. Santa Monica: Ingram, November 1992. pp. 98. (Box 7, Folder 262)
    Edited by Marvin Scott Jarrett.
    Contributions by Amy Cohen, Spike Jonze and Matt Mahurin.
    Article of note: "Ironic Youth."
    Design by David Carson.
  - Redaction. Number One. Ann Arbor, Michigan: Redaction, 2006. pp. 96. (Box 5, Folder 185)
    Edited by Ryan Molloy.
    Contributions by Ed Fella, Gloria Lee and Kenneth Fitzgerald.
    Article of note: "Visualingual."
  - Reflections: The Society of Learning Journal on Knowledge, Learning and Change. Volume One: Number One. Cambridge, Massachusetts: MIT Press, 1999. pp. 96. (Box 5, Folder 186)
    Edited by Edgar Schein.
    Contributions by Russell Ackoff, Arie de Geus and Stella Humphries.
    Article of note: "Metanoic Organizations in the Transition to a Sustainable Society."
    Cover photograph by Linda Cooper.
  - Renegade: A Literary Magazine Dedicated To New Writing of Excellence. Number One. New York: Renegade Magazine, 1978. pp. 78. (Box 5, Folder 187)
    Edited by Steven Fraccaro.
    Contributions by Walter Abish, Larry Eiger and Ron Silliman.
    Article of note: "Benjamin Obscura."
    Design by Annie Troy.
  - Rethinking Design. Issue 1. Cohoes, New York: Mohawk Paper Mills, 1992. pp. 80. (Box 5, Folder 188)
    Edited by Michael Bierut.
    Contributions by Delphine Hirasuna, Erik Spiekermann and Dana Arnett.
    Article of note: "Waiting for Permission."
  - Reviews of Geophysics. Volume 1: Number 1. Richmond, Virginia: American Geophysical Union, February 1963. pp. 126. (Box 5, Folder 189)
    Edited by Gordon MacDonald.
    Contributions by Thomas Farley, R. Lingenfelter and Peter Musen.
    Article of note: "The Growth of Knowledge of the Earth's Outer Radiation Belt."
  - Rolling Stone. Volume 1: Number 1. San Francisco: Straight Arrow Publishers, November 9, 1967. pp. 24. (Box 7, Folder 263)
    Edited by Jann Wenner.
    Contributions by Michael Lydon, Tedy Newhall and Susan Lydon.
    Article of note: "The High Cost of Music and Love: Where's the Money from Monterey?"
    Design by John Williams.
  - Rumor. Issue 01.01. Princeton, New Jersey: Princeton University School of Architecture, Winter 2010. pp. 8. (Box 5, Folder 190)
    Contributions by Joy Knoblauch, Marc McQuade and Stan Allen.
    Article of note: "Non-standard: David Adjaye with Teresita Fernádez and Marc McQuade."
    Cover art by Philip Tidwell.